Welcome to englobes Media Channels. In this video, we will explore the
meaning of the English phrase blow up.
Blow up means to explode or to cause something to explode,
often resulting in destruction or damage. Example the
terrorists planned to blow up the building with a bomb.
In the next clip, we will see an angry bird who used to blow up.
Now, bomb started with us two weeks ago.
Tell us your story, Bomb.
Okay, well, sometimes when I get upset,
I have been known to blow
up. So like what? Like you get mad, you mean?
Well, no, I literally blow up, okay? I explode
like a bomb.
Hence the name survive.
Excuse me? Party foul.
Do it. No can do. I just went boom boom before class.
Hey, look, I don't want to be here at all, but this could maybe make
it a little more interesting to me. So please? It explode.
You can't do it, can you? Yes, I can. But I'm having back
issues today, so I'm going to have to take a rain check.
Do it. Not the timer. Place the amigo. These guys are all nuts.
Big man.
Are we speaking telepathically or you're just good
talk.
englobes-- time :+0
conf : 0.4363
resulting-- time :+11
conf : 0.66533
bomb.-- time :+17
conf : 0.6187
we-- time :+19
conf : 0.65486
bomb-- time :+23
conf : 0.58803
blow-- time :+36
conf : 0.6893
like-- time :+38
conf : 0.50777
what?-- time :+38
conf : 0.52722
no,-- time :+40
conf : 0.68244
literally-- time :+41
conf : 0.69583
I-- time :+43
conf : 0.6
a-- time :+45
conf : 0.5
bomb.-- time :+45
conf : 0.45817
Hence-- time :+50
conf : 0.39726
survive.-- time :+55
conf : 0.12016
boom-- time :+69
conf : 0.69886
please?-- time :+74
conf : 0.51175
It-- time :+74
conf : 0.55091
explode.-- time :+74
conf : 0.53867
back-- time :+78
conf : 0.67564
I'm-- time :+80
conf : 0.28764
Do-- time :+83
conf : 0.57229
timer.-- time :+84
conf : 0.30678
the-- time :+85
conf : 0.58
talk.-- time :+95
conf : 0.56839