Welcome to Englobe's Media Channels. In this video, we will
explore the meaning of the English word unite.
Unite means to come or bring together for a common purpose
or action. Example the two companies decided
to unite their resources and expertise to develop a new product that neither
could have accomplished alone. In the next clip,
we will see two people unite to fight a large group.
Um,
I tell you, we ain't gonna want to be here when this thing goes off.
Slushy's 400 yards through the slide. They hold her in
some sort of medical timer set for 45 minutes. We get in and get
out. Blow this death. Fight for the pieces. Remember the hallway.
No guns. Right. Those guys have to be alive, because at the
end of the hallway, the retinal scanner needs a match to open the door.
Pick a door. All right, then. No, that's my door. It's better
with you.
I made a mistake. This is your door. Oh, no. No backseat.
What's the matter? You got a lot of bad guys behind that door? What's this?
You want to learn something?
Corresponding match. Access. Did I
access? Deny access
did.
Englobe's-- time :+0
conf : 0.46139
Unite-- time :+7
conf : 0.68861
to-- time :+14
conf : 0.66
resources-- time :+15
conf : 0.65982
could-- time :+18
conf : 0.50381
have-- time :+18
conf : 0.66533
In-- time :+20
conf : 0.6188
people-- time :+22
conf : 0.68595
to-- time :+23
conf : 0.69
large-- time :+24
conf : 0.62609
Um,-- time :+25
conf : 0.54889
Slushy's-- time :+33
conf : 0.16756
the-- time :+35
conf : 0.64
slide.-- time :+35
conf : 0.42571
They-- time :+36
conf : 0.51
Blow-- time :+40
conf : 0.53483
for-- time :+41
conf : 0.60876
guys-- time :+45
conf : 0.62609
have-- time :+45
conf : 0.57369
It's-- time :+53
conf : 0.59687
No-- time :+62
conf : 0.535
backseat.-- time :+63
conf : 0.39273
You-- time :+67
conf : 0.56397
match.-- time :+164
conf : 0.34156
Did-- time :+166
conf : 0.57453
Deny-- time :+168
conf : 0.22798
did.-- time :+172
conf : 0.52133